hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
Infiltrate:
the Set Trap
How is she?
I don't know why
she suddenly collapsed...
I see.
The collection ships depart
in the morning.
We should get back to the inn.
But then,
what will happen to Isaribi?
Who cares?
She's the Demon of the Ocean!
But...
Naruto, what in the world happened
with you and that girl?
Aw, c'mon! I told you
a little while ago, she saved me!
What happened?
Sorry, my hand slipped.
I see.
I'll clean this up right away.
Anko.
Yes?
The studies here,
the Hokage knows about them.
I understand.
So, you're saying that this girl
named Isaribi saved you?
Yeah, I owe my life to her.
Even if that's so, there's no doubt
that this girl named Isaribi
was one of the people
who attacked us.
Our mission is to protect
the government's money
and catch the Demon of the Ocean.
That's right, and no matter
how you look at it,
there's no doubt that
she's the Demon of the Ocean!
Yeah, but I think there's some reason
for all that.
I'm going to follow her and...!
You're talking nonsense.
Besides, even if we were to follow her,
we've got no idea where she is.
No, I have one.
Really, Shino?
It's something I heard.
It seems there's one island
in this country
that played a role in a series
of spiriting away incidents.
Where is it?!
A deserted island where
the Demon of the Ocean lives,
Demon Island.
Demon Island?
Sensei, are you doing okay?
Yes, more importantly,
there's something I want to tell you
about the Demon of the Ocean.
The true identity of this thing called
the Demon of the Ocean
is a human whose flesh
has been altered.
What?!
What did you say?
Don't muck things up like that again.
Yes, sir.
She's out, the monster!
What the...?
— Get out of here.
— You're bad luck.
Take this!
She's the one who was spirited away.
And why would she be
the only one who came back?
What are you talking about?
A spiriting away that occurred
ten years ago in the Land of Sea,
but that was not the working
of a demon.
Orochimaru kidnapped humans
to use as live subjects
for his research at the time.
Orochimaru...
Is Orochimaru mixed up
in this current matter?
Wait a minute.
Orochimaru and tests!
Why are you suddenly
saying such things?
I have to explain it to you from
when Orochimaru left the village.
Over ten years ago,
Orochimaru's desire to satisfy his own
inquiring mind and further his power
was such that he gradually
exceeded the scope of a Shinobi
and in the end, got involved in developing
what are called Forbidden Jutsu.
How unfortunate.
Naturally, this soon became
known to the village.
After Orochimaru!
Stop that guy!
But Orochimaru, who travelled
in and out of country on missions...
had several other private facilities
outside of the Leaf Village...
So one of those is on Demon Island?
So, the people who disappeared?
They were used for
human experiments.
What?
Damn Orochimaru!
What does he think people are?
So, what are we going to do?
It's obvious, isn't it?
We get into their hideout!
And we have to get Isaribi back!
It's settled.
We'll continue and hit
the Demon of the Ocean's hideout.
Sensei, how long have you known
about Demon Island?
It's because Orochimaru
was the Jonin in charge of me.
Tell me when we get close
to the island.
The pain is gradually getting stronger.
Somebody's coming.
What shall we do?
Do as you please.
Yes.
The arrogance...
One day I'll pay him back!
This way.
Hurry!
How is it, Shino?
No problem.
Okay!
So, a collection ship
is on the move, huh?
Just the right time.
Good work, I was right to send you
back to Mother Island.
What's wrong? You're pale.
When will I return to normal?
Like you said, I've gathered
information about the ships
from the market
and the village, even the attacks.
So...
What are you bringing up, Isaribi?
You can't possibly have forgotten
your role as a prototype.
As a converted body,
your cooperation in generating data...
That was one
of the conditions of the promise.
Don't worry, we'll soon be done
getting data from you.
I'll keep the promise...
as long as I don't change my mind.
You understand, right?
Yes.
Well, if you understand,
go keep our guests company.
I understand...
You're vicious, too.
There's no sign of 'em.
What is this?
Birds, no fish?
Don't move!
Too bad, isn't it?
Don't mess with Shinobi
from the Leaf Village.
You, little...!
Well, well,
aren't these cute kitties?
Is everyone okay?
Yep.
As always, you people
are addicted to peace.
You're from last evening!
Your face looks familiar.
The Chunin Exams,
if I remember correctly.
That's right...
As I recall, Sasuke's adversary!
The guy who was with
that Kabuto?!
You are correct...
Of course,
I haven't seen him since then.
You used a strange Jutsu
to suck up other's Chakras.
You're the guy who sucked up
all of Sasuke's strength.
Well, all of you, come at me.
I'm different than I was then.
Okay, I'll finish you off right now!
Wait, Naruto!
Shino?
You go ahead.
Seems like I'm the opponent for him.
His Jutsu is not suited for
your style of close combat.
We can't have all three of us stay here.
All right.
— We're counting on you, Shino!
— Be careful!
Wait!
Parasitic Insects, eh?
Found him!
Who?
Welcome, or should I say,
haven't seen you in a while?
It's you, Amachi.
I'm surprised!
I can't believe you've come back
after something like that happened...
Like what?
You don't remember?
Sorry, but I have no business
with you...
Where is Orochimaru?
Orochimaru?
Don't play dumb.
He's here, isn't he?
A Curse Mark responds even
though the operator isn't around...
Stuff like that happens, huh?
True, Orochimaru was here...
But that was over a month and a half ago.
No way.
It doesn't matter if you don't
believe me.
So the pain I felt so far...
has been the influence of Orochimaru's
presence here a month and a half ago?
Wait a minute.
Sensei!
You two!
Oh, my, you brought Genin.
Anko, you're all grown up...
Who is that?
Amachi... a Medical Ninja
who partnered with Orochimaru,
and was running
various experiments here.
Orochimaru's not here.
This whole incident was all his doing.
Him?!
Hey you! How dare you run
those ridiculous tests!
Ridiculous? This is no joke,
I've devoted my life to this research.
What was that?!
Look! This one has the physical ability
to adapt to water.
She combines the ability
to breathe underwater
and the muscle strength
to move freely and quickly.
It's been a dream of mine
for many years,
to form a Ninja corps
for underwater combat.
This is the first step.
A Ninja corps for underwater combat?
That's right, a military corps able
to move freely underwater
that the common person
definitely could not imitate.
When that happens,
we can divide land and land
and completely control
marine shipping routes!
Wonderful, is it not?
With this strength,
I'll stand on top of the world.
And I'll make Orochimaru regret
abandoning this research.
People are not your tools!
Oh, my, you're so young,
you don't understand the greatness
of this research...
Well, you're average guinea pigs
who don't know any better,
so I don't think I want you to understand.
Bastard!
That's good, Isaribi.
Out of the way, Isaribi!
No!
What's wrong? You can't fight
by just running around in circles.
Damn it!
Why are you protecting that guy?
That guy did this to you, Isaribi!
Yeah, but...!
But it can't be helped.
This is the only person who can
return my body back to normal.
He promised.
Look.
Isaribi...
People are judged based solely
on their appearance.
People don't dare come near me
just from being covered in bandages...
A monster with these scales
would be out of the question.
I want to return to my former body,
I want to be a human!
For that reason,
I decided I'd do anything!
You're a human being even now, Isaribi!
And yet you join with those guys
to attack and sink ships.
Isn't that far more like something
a monster would do?!
Stop it, shut up!
I... I...
I don't want to hear it!
Shut up, shut up!
Stop it! Are you bullying me, too?
No... I... I'm the same as you!
You're lying!
What are you talking about?
You're a normal human.
I want to be like you, too!
Don't cry, Isaribi...
I'll properly return you to normal.
Watch out!
A bullseye letter bomb.
Thanks to Isaribi doing a good job
of attracting your attention.
Sensei...
I'll leave the rest to you.
Okay.
Let's go, Isaribi.
Wait!
Don't go, Isaribi!
Damn it!
We'd better take care of
this right away.
Give it up... It's over.
We'll make you a guinea pig
for Amachi, too.
Insect clone?!
We're the same
Chakra-eating colleagues, after all.
It won't be easy to finish a fight.
He disappeared?
What is he thinking?
There you go!
Naruto!
I'm going to strangle you
to death like this.
What...?!
Mind Destruction Jutsu, a success.
All right, you did it, Ino!
Damn it! Let me go, let me go!
That's dirty of you!
What are you talking about?
There are no such things as
being too dirty or crappy for Shinobi.
And you call yourself a Ninja?
Shut up!
What?
This place is collapsing.
They're planning to take care
of us along with the building.
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me!
Hurry, the entrance is
already useless.
I thought this place would
be traced soon.
It's an old building,
but a damn good tomb
for the likes of them.
One person didn't make it in time?
Oh, well, doesn't have much of an
influence on attacking a collection ship.
Damn! Where's the exit?!
kaze ga fuite aa
the wind blows
itai kienai omoi
the pain, the memories won't disappear
nani wo motte ikou ka
what should be brought along?
atsumete hitotsu
assemble them into a piece
nido to nai nido to nai
there is no second chance, never
suteru nante baka mitai
how foolish it is to throw away
mujaki ni natte aa
acting so innocently
imeeji
the images
kitto sore wa owaranai
it probably will not end
ai no mune kogase
burn that love-filled heart
sen no yume watare
sail across a thousand dreams
juuoumujin kakete
running freely
te ni tsukamu sekai
to take hold of the world in hand
kumo ga chigirete
the clouds scatter
hi ga mata ochite
the sun sets yet again
hitori no pareedo ga ugokidasu
the solo parade begins to move
bouken kichijitsu shinpaku joushou
adventure, lucky day, geart beat, rising
meian souguu seimei souai
decisive, encounter, life, mutual love
Well, where's the exit, Shino?!
How should I know?
Then, what do we do, Ino?!
We just have to stop complaining
and run!
But I don't see an exit at all!
It seems the exit has collapsed.
- What?!
Are we going to be buried alive?!
— No!
— Since it's come to this...
- I'll use my Rasengan!
- What're you doing?
- How can you be calm?!
- Oh, shut up!
You guys step back a little!
Next time:
"Despair: A Heart Torn Apart."